I've tried to make this video a million times without literally screaming into my camera and seeming like a maniac, but I can't help it.
That's just who I am. You guys know me for being loud.
And there's one thing I'll never fucking be is loud and wrong.
And I'll always stand up for what's right.
And yes, I've only learned about this in the past month, October 7th.
And you know what? I'm glad that fucking Israelis cry that much because it reached my ears too.
They want to sit there and fucking cry and do a smear campaign on Palestinians
and want to act like they want to chalk up 75 years into one fucking day.
Jesus Christ.
And they want to call it a 9-11.
Oh God, they want to call it a 9-11.
And everybody knows what happened after 9-11.
The only people who found this situation confusing were the people who believed
that the Americans were really threatened by terrorists during 9-11,
even though they fucking caused it.
And killed a million people after the fact.
And then added TSA to make everybody fucking scared.
My God, all they're trying to do is scare you, fear-monger, war-monger,
and separate you from your own humanity.
That's it.
After learning about what happened in Palestine,
it's very clear to see, it is not confusing at all,
very clear to see who's the higher power and who's the oppressed.
How come a country that's only been around for 75 years has the fourth largest military?
How come?
How come they're getting aid from America, $3 billion a year,
and the minute they had a thing happen, America runs over there and helps them.
But you got people over here saying they're scared to go outside.
Meanwhile, I go outside, I see Israeli flags, no fucking problem.
People put up the Palestinian flag, they lose their jobs, they lose, they get doxxed,
they lose their managements, they lose their agencies, they lose friends,
they lose so many things.
And they've already lost their entire fucking families.
How much more do Palestinians have to lose for Israelis to be satisfied?
I would love to know.
They lose their homes, they lose everything, they lose their names, their children,
their mothers, their fathers.
To say that this is only October 7th is a sin.
To say that this is a war is a sin.
It is shameful to call this a war when there is no military on the other side.
And it's even more disgusting when I hear people try to shit on fucking Muslims,
saying, why doesn't their Muslim brothers take them in?
Nobody wants to take them in, that's the type of people they are, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Why do they have to leave?
Why have you never asked that question?
Why do they have to leave their own home?
If you have to leave your own home, would you just get the fuck up and go?
No, the hell you wouldn't.
So why do Palestinians have to leave their own home?
I want to know that question.
And if you want to sit there and condemn Hamas and condemn Hamas
and make it seem like terrorist, terrorist, I hate this fucking word terrorist.
I can't stand this word because it's only used on Muslims.
I haven't heard that word terrorist used from any other freaking nation, color, or religion.
Only Muslims get the word terrorist.
Why?
Why do you not question these things when you read them?
And all the propaganda coming from Israel.
Them calling it a 9-11 was the biggest red flag.
The minute I seen that, I said, oh, word, I already know what the fuck is going on over there.
But I wanted to make sure I was educated before I made a video.
Because when I started talking, I started fucking screaming.
I started going fucking crazy.
Real life.
Because I don't stand for this shit.
I'm pro-Palestine till it's backwards.
My heart is in Palestine.
You see these people dying.
You see these people losing their bloodlines.
You see the long list of names.
You see the babies dead.
You see children holding dead children.
You see children losing limbs.
You see fathers holding their...
Fathers are dying.
Mothers are dying.
Grandparents are outliving the freaking rest of their own generation.
There's a second knockabout happening right now.
And you're telling me that this is...
You're sitting here and telling me that you can stand with a country that's doing that to someone else.
And they're not just doing it to the Palestinians.
They're sending aid to Azerban to do it to the Armenians too.
So this shit is making no sense.
How a country could have this much fucking power.
This much influence on other countries to help them.
And it doesn't make you question in one second even though they've already been around for 75 years.
It doesn't make you question anything.
Really.
You're not seeing the same coin?
On both sides?
Our president right now is supporting a genocide?
And you're telling...
And you're gonna sit there and say, you know, Republicans are the only ones who like war?
Let's be real.
Let's be fucking real.
There's an agenda going on.
And it's unfortunate that it has to do with taking the lives of others.
It is so shameful to see and the hate that I've been seeing and to say it's only happening overseas and Islam phobia is on the rise over here.
And sure, anti-Semitism is also on the rise.
But the thing is, those Zionists, they're protected by our law.
It's systematic protection.
So when you know about systematics, you know who's really fucking being protected.
You know who's really fucking oppressed.
Think about it.
Really think about it.